module DeckSeed

  presidents = Deck.create!(subject: 'Presidents', creator_id: 1)
  disney = Deck.create!(subject: 'Disney', creator_id: 2)
  spanish = Deck.create!(subject: 'Spanish', creator_id: 3)
  french = Deck.create!(subject: 'French', creator_id: 4)
  disney_characters = Deck.create!(subject: 'Disney Characters', creator_id: 2)


  presidents.cards.create!(answer: "human or animal teeth; ivory; lead - never wood", question: "At his inauguration, George Washington only had 1 tooth. At different times, he wore dentures. What were his dentures made of?")
  presidents.cards.create!(answer: "John Quincy Adams", question: "A female reporter wanted to get an interview with this President but he refused because she was a woman. Every morning, he would swim naked in the Potomac River. One morning, she sat on his clothes and wouldnâ€™t move until she got the interview. She did. Who was the President?")
  presidents.cards.create!(answer: "Thomas Jefferson", question: "After his inauguration, this President went back to the house for dinner but there were no more seats left. No one offered him a seat but after a while, the wife of a Kentucky senator asked him if he wanted to sit.")
  presidents.cards.create!(answer: "Andrew Jackson", question: "Which President was the 1st to survive an assassination attempt? An unemployed house painter, Richard Lawrence, fired a pistol at him but it misfired. The 2nd pistol did the same. He then ran after Lawrence and beat him with his cane.")
  presidents.cards.create!(answer: "Martin van Buren", question: "Which President and his wife spoke Dutch at home?")
  presidents.cards.create!(answer: "Zachary Taylor", question: "Which President got his nomination for President late because he refused to accept any letters that had him pay postage due?")
  presidents.cards.create!(answer: "John Tyler", question: "After leaving office, who was so poor he was unable to pay a bill for $1.25 until he sold his corn crop?")
  presidents.cards.create!(answer: "cirrhosis of the liver - he drank a lot", question: "What did Franklin Pierce die from?")
  presidents.cards.create!(answer: "Andrew Johnson", question: "Which President did not know how to read, write and do math until his wife taught him?")
  presidents.cards.create!(answer: "throat cancer - he smoked 7-10 cigars a day", question: "What did Ulysses S. Grant die from? What did he do during his life that caused this?")

  disney.cards.create!(answer: "Lucy, Edmund, Peter & Susan Pevensie", question: "What four children are from Finchley?")
  disney.cards.create!(answer: "Valiant", question: "Lofty, Bugsy & Toughwork are feathered friends from what animated feature?")
  disney.cards.create!(answer: "Cinderella", question: "The phrase Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo is from a song in what movie?")
  disney.cards.create!(answer: "Maid Marian", question: "In Robin Hood, who does Robin fall in love with?")
  disney.cards.create!(answer: "Oliver and Company", question: "Georgette was a prissy poodle in what Disney feature?")
  disney.cards.create!(answer: "Hades", question: "What character from Disney's Hercules has blue flames as hair?")
  disney.cards.create!(answer: "Pinocchio", question: "In what feature can the song Hi-Diddle-Dee-Dee be heard?")
  disney.cards.create!(answer: "Vixey", question: "Who does Tod fall in love with in the Fox and the Hound?")
  disney.cards.create!(answer: "A.A. Milne", question: "Who wrote the original Winnie the Pooh series")
  disney.cards.create!(answer: "Pipe", question: "In The Little Mermaid, what does Scuttle call a snarfblatt?")

  spanish.cards.create!(answer: "Night", question: "Noche")
  spanish.cards.create!(answer: "Water", question: "Agua")
  spanish.cards.create!(answer: "Locker or Closet", question: "Armario")
  spanish.cards.create!(answer: "4", question: "Cuatro")
  spanish.cards.create!(answer: "1", question: "Uno")
  spanish.cards.create!(answer: "2", question: "Dos")
  spanish.cards.create!(answer: "3", question: "Tres")
  spanish.cards.create!(answer: "5", question: "cinco")
  spanish.cards.create!(answer: "6", question: "seis")
  spanish.cards.create!(answer: "7", question: "siete")

  french.cards.create!(answer: "yes", question: "oui")
  french.cards.create!(answer: "a", question: "un")
  french.cards.create!(answer: "an", question: "une")
  french.cards.create!(answer: "some", question: "des")
  french.cards.create!(answer: "I", question: "je")
  french.cards.create!(answer: "not", question: "pas")
  french.cards.create!(answer: "this", question: "ce")
  french.cards.create!(answer: "no", question: "non")
  french.cards.create!(answer: "me", question: "moi")
  french.cards.create!(answer: "to see", question: "voir")

  disney_characters.cards.create!(answer: "Snow White", question: "The original Disney Princess")
  disney_characters.cards.create!(answer: "Grumpy", question: "The grouchiest dwarf")
  disney_characters.cards.create!(answer: "Queen Grimhilde", question: "Wanted a person's heart in a box")
  disney_characters.cards.create!(answer: "Pinocchio", question: "He wants to be a real boy")
  disney_characters.cards.create!(answer: "Geppetto", question: "The 'father' of the living puppet")
  disney_characters.cards.create!(answer: "Blue Fairy", question: "When you wish upon a star, this female appears")
  disney_characters.cards.create!(answer: "Monstro", question: "The whale that swallowed the puppet")
  disney_characters.cards.create!(answer: "Dumbo", question: "The flying elephant")
  disney_characters.cards.create!(answer: "Bambi", question: "The faun whose mother was killed")
  disney_characters.cards.create!(answer: "Thumper", question: "The rabbit named for his habit")
end

